Well, we have, I believe, the best cakes, the best site and it's all looking super amazing.
So we've got our two pages.
But there's one thing that's remaining because a website is not just a web page or web pages separated.
They need to be connected.
So we want to be able to click on that fellow there and we want to get through to this page.
So how do we do it.
Heading back to the HTML remember we've got our two pages.
That's our carrot cake page.
This is our main page which would be called our home page.
And we want to connect the two okay.
So we've got this option that gives us um an option to link to link pages.
Yes.
Yes okay.
So over here this is where we've got our moist carrot cake.
So I'm first going to show you this link option.
So if you go let's actually do it right at the bottom just to give an example.
So if we say a tag and just type in a go there.
So this is called an anchor tag.
It's allowing you to anchor and link something to something else.
Yeah.
So what?
This is going to be our website name.
So we want to link it to this.
Say that.
So now this is where see inside these little inside the inverted commas we're going to pop in there.
And then this is this is what you're going to see.
So if it's text it's going to be like the carrot cake or whatever.
It doesn't really matter right now.
See this is just text.
So now if we refresh that you'll see with text it'll be in blue.
Okay.
Now you know you're very familiar with those.
You see those little underlined things.
And yes, there we go.
When you clicked on hey, what did it do?
It brought us through to that page.
So that's your old familiar hyperlink text underlined.
It brings us through to the new page.
So that's how simple it is.
So all that it was is using this a tag putting the link and then whatever the text was.
So but that's not really what we want to do Josh.
We want to actually link it linked to the image, not to some random bit of text at the end there.
So actually this is actually really easy.
All we're going to do, we can take that actually.
Um, and then we'll go here, which is where we have our image.
And then inside this we're going to put our image.
So after TD just put that in and use the A tag.
Yep.
Swapping hey just to get rid of the hey.
Yeah.
And then image it ends image right there.
We're going to take that and we're going to put it inside the tag I'll put it inside.
So instead of having the text inside the A tag, we are putting in our image tag inside the A tag.
So we're going to have a little bit of extra thing there.
Um, okay.
So we save that now when we refresh okay.
So nothing looks different except as you see when we go here, nothing.
When we go there, we've got the finger right.
Give it the finger Now when we click it.
Yeah, baby.
We're rocking.
It almost looks like.
Like you can see the same image brings it there.
It's the.
What's the word for it?
Yes.
Okay, but you know what?
Actually, why not also add the link to that moist carrot cake?
So at the moment, if I click there, nothing's going to in the wrong page.
Nothing's going to happen if you click there anyway.
But if you click here nothing's going to happen.
It'd be cool if that was also maybe hyperlinked.
So if we wanted to do both.
So what we can do is we just have to take this.
Well, we could put the a tag here as well.
So you could just do another A tag for.
Yeah I know moist carrot cake could copy it.
But we've got so much stuff in it.
We just do another.
You've gone, you've gone and put it inside the H3.
Okay.
So put it in a space a tag.
Now we get all of this.
We get this little word here.
you drop them inside?
Yeah.
Done wrong.
Done.
Very wrong.
There we go.
Fantastic.
Yeah, you got it there.
You've got it there.
You're rocking.
Yeah.
Okay, so now when we refresh, there we go.
So now we've got a hyperlink on both of them.
So if you click either one you're going to come through to the wrong page.
Ah you're a, you're a that is not intelligent.
Yeah I haven't put any links in.
So yes that's very clever.
All you've done is you've put in a moist carrot cake.
That's brilliant.
All in the mistakes.
Yeah.
There we go.
And now it brings you through.
So there we go.
So that's looking fantastic.
So at this stage we basically have got a complete website.
You have got all your images.
You can see them.
You can embed them.
We have got backgrounds.
We've got logos.
We've got clickable links.
We've got second pages.
We've got tables used for formatting.
We've got embedded videos.
This is fantastic.
I just think there's one more thing.
No way.
One more thing.
You know, you're starting to sound like what's his name?
From Apple.
And there's just one more thing.
It's not a good one.
Come on, Steve.
It's not a big thing.
It's the new iPhone.
What is it?
It's just going to be.
So when we click on this image, we don't really want to have to click the back button.
So what we can do.
Yeah.
Like a button that.
But that's a little arrow.
Yeah I've got it.
Okay.
So I've got handy in my finder a little arrow right here.
You might not be the best one, but you know arrow is an arrow.
So we'll just again you can go to Pixabay.
You can find arrows and whatever you like there.
Whatever.
Let's just put this in.
It's going to be near the top somewhere.
Yeah I'll just put it right at the top on the on the body.
Yeah.
So under the body, we could even do the head because it is kind of, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know.
Let's just do it on the body.
Let's do the body.
We can see how that looks.
Okay.
So so it's an image pasted in.
Stick the name in there.
Save it.
Okay.
So now this is just going to save a.
It's a big baby.
But can we just like yeah I'm gonna have to swollen that down a bit smaller than that I like to that.
It's smaller than that.
Yeah.
With equals.
What should we do at 30.
30 ish.
That's kind of small.
Let's do 260.
No.
That's much.
It's gonna be like massive.
No it's not, it is.
It's gonna be okay.
Look, she's going to be wrong.
I told you he's wrong.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay, I'll set 45.
Yes.
Okay.
What?
She doesn't want to listen.
Watch.
Watch 45.
45.
Okay.
It's a little small again.
82, 130.
Ah.
always wants to go to bed.
82 would be Donny.
Yeah.
That's good.
Okay, now we have to link it.
I don't know.
It's sort of stuck on top of my logo now, but anyway.
No.
It's good.
Yeah, their logo is just a little thing.
Um, so you can see how long you can spend fiddling with these things, but you get the idea, right?
So we stuck in our little arrow as a back arrow.
But it's not just an image we want.
We also need to use the anchor tag because we want to make it a hyperlink.
Yeah.
So we're going to have to go there at a hyperlink.
And it's going to hyperlink back to uh this page here.
Save that and we put it in there.
So now finally the website is actually looking really good.
Click there.
There.
We've got nice easy access.
And when you hit it yeah.
Back.
Oh one more thing Steve.
You're a bit.
Hey that was fantastic.
Now we can go.
Look, we've just made a chocolate cake.
We're going to go look for some more ones?
The best part is.
But you guys can't see this.
We've actually got a real chocolate cake waiting for us.
A mixture of carrot and everything.
I think we're going to go and eat that right now.
This is one time you can have your cake and eat it.
So there, we've got it.
A best chocolate cake website you could ever want.
And you've got the idea.
You have got the skills.
You've got the ability to create your own website.
So hopefully you have learned lots of amazing and incredible things.
It's really simple.
This is the start of an incredible journey.
Uh, learning to to code, learning to use HTML is really, really exciting.
So we hope that you've had lots of fun.
Get out there.
The best way to learn is to play.
Have fun, make mistakes.
That's okay.
Create things.
Let's see how they work.
Try it.
And most of all, share it with us.
Tell us what you want, what doesn't work?
What does work?
What else you would like to try?
We'd love to learn as well from you.
So it's a learning journey.
We want to be in it with you together and we hope you've had lots of fun.
So get out there.
Give it a try.